

2524 Sandy Ridge Lane Charlotte, North Carolina, 28105 abreckwoldt23@gmail.com 704-618-7423 Website: https://www.awoldt.com/

Website: https://www.awoldt.com/ GitHub: https://github.com/awoldt

My name is Alex Breckwoldt, and I'm a full-stack developer from Charlotte, NC. I enjoy building web applications with Node.js and Golang and have built a portfolio of all my work over the past three years. I deeply understand OOP programming and can adapt to any tech stack needed. My goal is to one day get a job in the tech industry.

Professional Experience

Package Handler Amazon | November 2019 - August 2021

At Amazon, I ensured that all packages that passed through the warehouse went to the correct spot and got to the customer on time. I worked at Amazon over the course of 3 years and learned a lot about how a significant company with thousands of moving parts operates.

Cashier Circle K | May 2019 - August 2019

At Circle K, I was tasked with checking out people efficiently and politely. Working at Circle K helped me establish customer skills and communication.

Kennel Assistant Monroe Road Animal Hospital | June 2015 - August 2015

Monroe Road Animal Hospital was the first formal job I ever had. I ensured all the dogs and cats boarding with us had an optimal living space and enough food and water.

Education

High School Diploma Butler High School at Matthews | August 2012 - June 2016

Bachelors in Management Information Systems University of North Carolina at Charlotte | August 2016- May 2022

Key Skills

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Node.js
- React.js
- Express.jsGoogle Cloud Platform
- MongoDB
- Go (Golang)
- Bootstrap
- Docker

Personal Projects

Below are some of the best personal projects I've worked on that showcase my frontend and backend development skills. You can find a complete list of all my projects on my GitHub.

StockWasp - Fully-fledged stock price and news web app built with Golang and styled with Bootstrap. Fetches real-time stock data on each request using Financial Modeling Prep's API.

https://stockwasp.com/

<u>WordleBin</u> - Remake of the popular web game Wordle. React.js frontend with complex nested component hierarchy. https://wordlebin.com/

<u>Spotify Music Dashboard</u> - Sign in to your Spotify account and visualize all your favorite music and artists on one page, along with music recommendations.

https://spotify-dashboard-ruby.vercel.app/

<u>Chat Applications</u> - Chat with friends over websocket connection. React.js frontend with Express.js backend. https://frontend-3e7sr4g6ia-uc.a.run.app/